(Raj:)Oh, yeah?
What if the earth was in danger
(Howard:)and the only way
to save it was to take a shower
(Raj:)in the locker room and let
other guys see you naked?
(Howard:)Oh, come on.
That's never gonna happen.
(Howard:)Put your hand
in the jar
(Howard:)or forever be revealed
as my sidekick.
(Raj:)All right, I will.
(Howard:)How did you get so brave
all of a sudden?
(Raj:)It's easy.
(Raj:)The spider's crawling
up your arm.
(Howard:)Get it off! Get it off!
(Howard:)Please, Raj!
(Howard:)Please.
(Howard:)Oh!
(Amy:)My blood work shows
thyroid function normal.
(Amy:)Cortisol levels normal.
(Sheldon:)How about your
(Sheldon:)follicle-stimulating hormone
levels?
(Amy:)Sheldon, I am not going
through menopause.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure?
(Sheldon:)You said that with
the testy bark of an old biddy.